Let's do this.
Yeah.
The stone... shattered.
Are you done yet, Fullmetal? We can't keep this up much longer!
This...
This has to be Edward.
I see. You did it, Fullmetal.
That transmutation circle on the pedestal was the last remnant of your human heart.
Crowley...
What? An earthquake?
This is bad! Let's get out of here now!
Mr. Arlen, what are you doing? Come on!
I will... I'll remain here.
What are you talking about?
You have to run. You'll be crushed here too!
It doesn't matter...
I've decided to share my fate here with Crowley and the others.
My final remaining duty has been fulfilled.
There's no longer any reason for me to keep living.
Crowley, Elma, and I were always together.
So, I think I’ll also rest peacefully with them here.
You idiot. I don’t know anything about your "final duty" or "always together," but that’s no reason for you to die too!
It's all right, I've already made up my mind.
Thank you. Fullmetal Alchemist.
Don't give me that! You think I'll let something so nightmarish happen to you right in front of me!? Al.
Okay.
Wh-What are you doing?! Stop it!
If you struggle too much, you might end up in my belly.
Hey, let me go!
Alright, let's go!
S-Stop, put me down! I... I...!
Elma...
All he wanted was to bring his beloved back to life.
Is this the end of a man's obsession?
What a tragedy...
Brother, what are you thinking about right now?
The same thing you are, Al.